- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
[all speaking foreign language]
- Whoo!
- This week is hometowns
and I'm really looking forward
to meeting
four amazing families.
- This house right here
is the house where I grew up.
- That means a lot
that you want me here.
- I knew right away,
"Oh, my God.
This is real."
- Do you feel like he's ready?
- I will admit,
you got me worried.
- Luke really lives his faith,
and we're on a good path.
- Somehow her heart
has softened to you.
And you know what?
That is a gift, like,
we could never deserve.
- Peter's heart
can get broken,
so I'm very nervous.
'Cause I know that
you're dating three other guys
and it scares me.
- I'm sorry.
I only want the best for you.
- I'm a mom,
a little guarded.
- I'm falling in love with him.
- Do you say that
to all of them?
She asked me if you'd be ready
to be engaged,
and I said no.
[dramatic music]
- It feels like
a very impossible situation.
- Are you okay?
- No.
♪ ♪
- It's all coming up tonight
on "The Bachelorette."
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- I'm so excited
to be back in California
just down the street
from the mansion.
This week is hometowns,
and I'm down to four guys.
And so I'm really
looking forward
to meeting
four amazing families.
This week is really
important to me
and to each
of my relationships
because I get to meet
the people that love them
and know them best
and see a little bit
of what makes each
of these guys who they are,
knowing that one of these men
hopefully is my husband.
This week is just
really important
to see what it would be like
to live life with this person.
Today is my first
hometown this week
and I could not
be more excited.
- Hello.
- I've got a date with Peter!
- Oh, God, I missed you
so much.
- I missed you.
- I can't believe
you're here right now.
[kisses]
Hello.
- Hey.
- This is awesome.
You're in
my hometown right now.
- I love it.
- I have a very fun day
planned for us.
- Yay.
- And I have a surprise that
I think that you're gonna like.
- Okay.
- But first let's go
for a little ride.
- Okay.
- Sound good?
- Let's do it.
- All right.
Let's go.
- Peter is so sweet.
Like, I can see, like,
the genuine excitement
every time he's with me.
And I just--I love it.
- This is so crazy
that you're here right now.
Like, I love this.
- I know!
I feel like when I was little
playing with my Barbie dolls,
Peter is the guy
I saw myself with.
He's like a handsome pilot
that's sweet and successful
and also sexy.
- So this is my baby.
- Okay.
- She's, uh--she's pretty fun.
And, uh, yeah.
Let's go for a little ride.
- Oh, okay.
- There we go.
- Cool.
But he wasn't
somebody initially, like,
right off the bat I was, like,
my eyes were, like, on.
He just kinda snuck up on me
and my emotions and my feelings
and so I'm trying to figure out
where he fits in my heart.
Oh, I'm pumped.
- Let's go.
Let's do it.
[car engine turns over]
It's a beautiful day
in Westlake Village
with my girl.
- Yes.
Today I just wanna get
more insight into his life.
[car engine revving]
[laughing]
- What's up?
- I'm gonna investigate
in here.
- You're investigating
in my car?
I think I'm out of Altoids.
I have gum, though.
[speaking Spanish]
- Who is this?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Aww.
- Definitely very blessed.
- [laughs]
- [whispers] What?
- What is that for?
- What?
- Why do you have a rubber?
- That--okay, let's, like,
not put that on camera.
- Heck, yeah!
- Wow, that's so
embarrassing right now.
- What do you think
is gonna happen in this car?
- What the--you--
oh, my God.
Just put this down.
That's so bad.
I am so mortified right now.
- That's awesome.
- Oh, boy.
- Peter.
- Yes.
- We're just holding hands
and kissing in this car.
- Oh, my God.
- You're a safe guy.
- I--I practice safety.
- Good.
- I'm safe in everything I do.
- Yeah.
- Flying and other stuff,
so...
- [laughs]
- Anyways, it's all good.
- [laughing]
[car engine revving]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Look at this.
- [gasps]
What the crap?
- Well, I, uh,
obviously am looking
for a copilot for life.
But how do you say, uh,
we, uh, have you be
my copilot for this flight,
huh?
You wanna fly?
- Yes.
Oh, my gosh!
- Let's go do it.
- This is gonna be so fun.
- I am falling so freaking fast
for Hannah.
Shall we go fly?
- Let's do it.
- [pat] Let's do it!
- Ooh!
Through our entire journey,
the way everything's progressed
has just been so amazing
and, like, finally getting
to this point now...
taking her flying,
sharing my passion.
I am just, like,
over the moon right now.
All right, here we go.
- Oh, gosh.
Yeah, you got me.
- You're stuck with me now.
- [laughs]
- Today is such
an amazing opportunity
for our relationship just
to soar to that next level.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Uh-oh.
[engine rumbling]
I'm so happy right now.
Let's go.
[engine revving]
[uplifting music]
Whoo!
- [laughing]
♪ ♪
[laughing]
- Oh!
♪ ♪
- I love flying.
It's my ultimate passion,
and the fact that I get
to share this with Hannah--
someone I am feeling
so strongly for--
it just means so much.
- Yeah!
- Look, look!
There's my boy!
Oh!
- I don't want this moment
to end, you know?
I just--I literally just wish
we could just fly all day long
and just, like,
hold her there in my arms.
♪ ♪
Whoo!
- Whoo!
- Yes.
That was so awesome.
- That was--that was hot.
- I love every second
I spend with Hannah
and being able to do
what we just did,
like, fly an airplane,
I could not
have asked for more.
Like, it was perfect.
I am crazy for Hannah.
[both cheering]
- [laughs]
- The way I feel with her,
no one's ever made me feel.
Not even close.
You are so special,
and I know
I tell you all the time,
but, like, I am falling, like,
crazy for you...
and today is, like,
such an important day
for me just with family
and, like, I can't wait,
you know?
To introduce you, like--
- I'm so excited.
- It's gonna be--
my family is obviously, like,
they're the most
important people, you know,
in my life,
and it's super important for me
just to have, like,
the support from my family
of the person I end up with.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Like, in the past
with my last ex,
they've been
extremely supportive
and my rock for me to lean on
through those hard times,
um, getting over that.
But I have not felt like this.
It's truly Heaven.
And I do see a future with you,
and I--
[chuckles]
The happiness that you give me
is just, like--
I've never felt this,
and I truly feel like
we have something special,
and I can't wait
for them to see that.
- I can't wait for them too.
- It's very important just
to have obviously
that approval from my family.
They're the most
important people to me.
What do you say we, uh,
hit the road?
- Let's do it.
- All right.
I've dated girls that weren't
right for me in the past.
So it's very important
to get that validation
from them as well.
- Okay.
- For me to know that they see
how much I truly value Hannah.
[birds chirping]
- Oh, look at the rose bush.
- This is it.
- Oh, I love it.
[mellow music]
- Welcome.
- I think he's--
- Hello, hello!
- Hi!
- Hello!
[all laughing]
- Oh, oh, oh!
- Hannah's gonna meet my dad,
Peter.
- Oh, oh!
- My mom, Barbara.
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- And then
my little brother Jack.
- So these are for you.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- You have the most
beautiful flowers, by the way.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- She's a big flower fan.
- Yeah.
- This is a huge deal for me.
I'm falling in love
with Hannah
but it's a little bit scary.
Like, I've never
brought someone home
that I've felt
so strongly for.
I'm just hoping that my family
can see the happiness
that Hannah brings me.
- So tell us about it.
Where have you guys been?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- [laughing] Can't wait to hear
all about it.
- We've had--seriously--like,
such an amazing journey.
Like, we--
- Oh, wait, I wanna say this.
- Okay.
- [laughs]
So, Peter--
I mean, he was so sweet.
But he was like,
"Just letting you know,
like, it takes me a while to,
like, open up."
And I was like, "Well, no.
"Like, I'm gonna
challenge you to, like,
"open up to me and, like,
I need to see you
"because I really am
excited about you.
But I need you to,
like, give me who you are."
And right after he was like,
"Okay."
He's like, "Yes, Ma'am."
- Challenge accepted.
- I can do this.
- And he changed, yeah.
- I had to.
I had to.
- And honestly, like,
every time that
we've been together,
it's just been, like...
- It's like magic.
- Great.
Yeah, like, perfect.
- Very nice.
- It's really awesome.
- Oh, my gosh.
Well, are you ready
for some Cuban food?
- Yes!
- Yes, we are.
- Yes.
- Hell yeah!
- Vamos a comer
como los Cubanos!
- Uh-huh.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- So, should we, uh--
- Well, we're gonna do a little
German prayer first real quick.
- Okay.
- So--
- All righty.
[all speaking German]
all: Let's eat!
- Let's eat!
- Whoo!
all: Whoo!
That's like, uh,
a German tradition that we do,
like, every meal.
- That's so fun.
- It's progressively gotten
louder over the years.
- What it means is,
"Happy is the mealtime feast,"
you know,
"with your loved ones.
Happy, happy, happy.
Let's eat."
- I love that.
- So let's--let's toast,
shall me?
- So this has been truly, like,
the most amazing journey
of my life and, like,
being able to meet Hannah
has just been,
like, such a blessing,
and here's to just
so many amazing memories
that we've made
and so many more to come.
I can't tell you how happy I am
that I get to introduce you
and have you here
with my family
'cause they mean
the world to me and, um...
[soft music]
[chuckles]
Like, just like, my, like--
my grandparents, you know,
[voice breaks] would, like,
have loved you, too,
and, like, Mama and...
[indistinct] and...
It just--this means lots,
so cheers.
all: Cheers!
- Cheers to that.
- Sorry, I'm good.
[all laughing]
I'm good.
- It's very special
for Peter to bring a girl home
and I could see that
he's super happy with her
and that's great.
All right, Hannah,
wanna go talk?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- All right, let's do this.
- Enjoy.
- But I know Peter
is a very all in when--
in his relationships,
and that's very scary
because he could have
his heart broken.
So I wanna see where Hannah
is with Peter.
Knowing Peter
and growing up with him,
I'm always the more
pragmatic one
and he's more
the hopeless romantic.
And so in his past
relationships
he's the type of person
that when he is gonna date,
he's gonna go all in
and be fully committed.
And when he gets all into you,
it's very hard for him
to get out of that.
- Yeah.
- And so have you guys talked
about your feelings?
Are you in love
with each other?
- Yeah.
Um, no, we haven't.
But I also wouldn't be here
if I didn't think
that my feelings are on the--
the track to be there.
- Mm-hmm.
- And to be able to say that.
So--
- No, of course, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Well, that's--
that's very refreshing.
- Yeah.
- You've got
to tell me everything.
Everything.
How do you feel about her?
- Yeah.
- Is she the one?
I mean, is this the one
that makes your heart go...
[singing]
You know, you gotta--
just tell me everything.
- Yeah.
Our connection has been so...
just like fire.
Like, so much passion
and, like,
every single time
I'm with her...
Like, I've dated girls
in the past.
I've never felt anywhere close
the way I feel for her.
- Are you in love with her?
- I--
[chuckles]
I'm definitely there.
I don't know.
Like, I'm falling for her
like crazy right now.
Like--
- I can see.
- It's--
- I can see that.
- It's--it's amazing.
- You think she's
in love with you?
- I don't know, but I know
how I feel about her,
and I have a good feeling
how she feels about me.
- Have you said I love you
to her yet?
- I have not said it yet.
Um, I...
Obviously from, you know,
my last relationship
and how hard that was
for me to move on
and truly, like, let that go,
and the fact
of the matter is, like,
there's three other guys still.
- Right.
- So it's not just me.
- It's not just you.
- But I know the connection
that Hannah and I have.
And I feel like I found
my person right now.
- I'm just so proud of you
because what's in that heart
of yours is so precious
and so special,
and I--I just want--
I want...
[dramatic music]
I want the world for you.
Peter's happiness
is everything to me.
I love you.
- I love you.
- I know that there's
a lot of love
on his part
going towards Hannah.
But I know that she's dating
three other guys
at the same time,
and I'm aware that
Peter's heart can
get broken again.
So I'm very nervous.
I have to tell you one
of the things that worries me
as a mom--'cause you know
how much I love him, right?
- Yeah.
- Is, you know, I know that--
I just had a talk with him.
- Mm-hmm.
- He's head over heels
over you.
And it scares me,
to be honest with you.
It scares me.
It scares me 'cause I know
that you're dating other--
three other guys.
I do know that.
And he's very--
everything is to his heart.
And I just worry, sweetie.
- Yeah.
- So I just wanted
to share that.
- Yeah.
I totally understand
being scared.
And I know that
he cares for me.
And I care for him a lot, too.
I can see that
it could be Peter and I
at the end of this.
Like, I wouldn't allow him
to invest his heart into me
if I didn't think that
the end could be him and I.
- [crying]
I'm just very emotional
right now.
- No--
- But I mean,
I just wish that...
God will find the path for you.
And of course, would I love it
to be with our son?
Absolutely, 'cause I'm really
in need of a daughter.
[both laughing]
- We would have a good time.
- Yeah.
- Sounds like you just had
a hell of a ride so far.
- This has been, like,
the most unbelievable journey.
It's been, like,
every time I'm with her,
it's just better and better
and better.
It's just amazing.
Like, our connection's
like so undeniable.
And then after
that flight today,
I just knew, like, I'm like,
"That's my person."
Like, I found my person.
And you guys know I've always
been a hopeless romantic.
- That's for sure.
- And I'm gonna follow
my heart and--
- That's for sure.
- Like I've told her
so many times,
I'm crazy about her.
- Does she know that?
- I haven't, like,
expressed to her, like,
the ultimate--
in the ultimate way but--
- You haven't told her that you
love her or anything like that?
- No, but I'm--I'm there.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Y-you know that there's
three other guys, right?
Are--are--are you prepared for
not continuing this journey?
- I mean, yeah, there's
a chance of heartbreak again
and obviously I--I
don't want that but, you know--
- Well, we don't--we don't
want that for you, either.
I--I know how much you suffered
in that relationship.
But you're opening
your heart again
and I--I can see that
you genuinely care for Hannah
and I--I can see
that she cares for you.
I mean, you guys
look wonderful together.
You know, you do.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- And I hope you get
what you're desiring.
I really do.
It's--it's nice to see.
It is.
It is nice to see.
Its, uh...
[emotional music]
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
- I get that.
♪ ♪
- You know I--I only want
the best for you.
♪ ♪
And...
that's it.
- I know you do.
- I just want the best for you.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- [chuckles]
It's so good to be back.
- Cheers.
- Peter is special because he
wears his heart on his sleeve
and I just want
the best for him.
♪ ♪
That's it.
- I'm so happy that you guys
know Hannah now
and, um, can just see, like,
how crazy I am for her.
- Que viva el amor.
- Viva el amor!
- Si, si.
- Amen to that.
- Amen.
- Today was magic in, like,
every sense of the word.
- See you, guys.
- Love you.
God bless you all.
- All right.
Love you guys.
- Bye.
- Blessings.
- See ya--blessings.
After just everything
that happened today,
you know, from sharing
my love of flying with her
and seeing her just
enjoy that so much,
and then having
that validation--
that support from my family,
I didn't think I could feel
any more sure about her.
But I do.
I'm definitely
in love with Hannah,
and I wanna truly
let her know that.
I'm so happy I was able
to share, you know,
flying with you and--and
showing you all those
special places, and I am...
Falling so freaking hard.
But I'm so okay with it,
and I...
I'm so happy
with where we're at.
And I just--I look forward
to the future with us and...
this is so perfect.
It's been so perfect
in so many ways.
[dramatic music]
I wanted to tell her so badly.
But as strongly as I feel,
it's scary.
Let's do it.
♪ ♪
You know, obviously I don't
know exactly where she's at,
where her heart's at.
The potential of again opening
up my heart to someone
and not having it work out
honestly is, like,
terrifying to me.
Well...
Come here.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- All right, baby.
I'll see you soon, all right?
[both laughing]
Okay.
- Okay, see you soon.
- See you.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Take good care of my girl.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Watching her drive away,
I do wish I had
said something.
I don't even know
what I'm waiting for.
I just--it's gonna--
when it feels right,
you know, it'll happen.
I just really hope
it's not too late.
- Coming up...
- There's no doubt
there's sexual attraction
between Tyler and I.
- Behave, now.
- But there have been
concerns for me
that Tyler's ready for next
steps in a relationship.
Do you feel like he's ready?
- I will admit you've
got me worried about him.
- Why are you worried?
- And later...
both: ♪ We are ♪
♪ Fallin' in love ♪
Whoo!
My family's blessing
is gonna propel
our relationship.
- She asked me upstairs if
you'd be ready to be engaged,
and I said no.
This is crazy.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- We are currently
in Jupiter, Florida
about to have my hometown
with Hannah Brown,
and I am so excited.
I'm excited for Hannah
to meet my family.
It's been weeks and weeks and
weeks since I've seen my dad.
I can't wait for Hannah
to meet him as well.
He's gonna fall
in love with her.
You made it.
- Hey.
- Mmm, my girl.
[chuckles]
I missed you.
- I'm so glad to be here.
We have made it.
Well, this is my hometown.
- I love it.
- It's beautiful.
- It's so beautiful.
- You're outshining
it right now,
but it's beautiful.
I can't wait
to show you my family.
- I'm so excited.
- It's gonna be a great day.
So, uh, the best way
to explore Jupiter
is by boat.
- Yes.
- And I got a boat
for us to go on.
And I promise you I'm better
and driving a boat
than I am riding a horse.
- Praise the Lord.
- So you'll be in good hands.
- [laughs]
- So let's get out of here.
- Let's do it.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Where do you want it?
- Um...
[laughs]
I don't care.
All over.
- Mmm.
♪ ♪
- There's no doubt there's...
[laughs]
some sexual attraction
between Tyler and I,
and I think he's super hot.
[laughs]
- Hey, now.
- But there have been
concerns for me
that Tyler's ready for, like,
next steps in a relationship.
- Is that good?
- Yeah, it's good.
But today I'm excited
to just see him in his element
and get to be a part of that.
- All right,
now time to do Jupiter.
- So pumped.
♪ ♪
- As a kid, man, we used to
rip through these waterways
all the time.
- So it's like this is your--
your place?
- This is my spot, yeah.
- It's so pretty.
- This is one of my favorite
restaurants right here.
I'll take you there one day.
Really good spot.
So this is where
we were earlier.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's our lighthouse.
- Isn't it for when
fishermen are out at sea
for them to know where
to come back home or something?
- Exactly.
- Back to their woman.
- Exactly, you know,
sometimes if I get lost,
I need my lady to get me,
you know?
♪ ♪
You know, this is my
little slice of paradise.
- I like it.
- Looks good on you.
Jupiter's everything to me.
And to see her just enjoy
and love it
and have fun gives me so much
confidence in us going forward.
- [screams]
♪ ♪
[light music]
It's super hot kissing Tyler.
It's--it's nice.
Tyler lives in a paradise,
so it's cool to think
that future with Tyler is--
is this.
- This house right here...
- Uh-huh.
- Is the house
where I grew up in.
And that's where pretty much
my childhood was at,
you know?
And then, like,
the recession hit
and we lost it
and it put us in a tough spot.
But we all got stronger
out of it, you know?
- Yeah.
- It really means a lot
to me and to have you here.
- It means a lot
that you want me here.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
To taking the reins over
and letting me lead
a date for once.
- Yes.
- And, uh, enjoying
this beautiful weather
with a beautiful girl.
- Aww, cheers.
- Cheers.
- And to just knowing more
about what makes Tyler Tyler.
- Yep, learning about
what makes Tyler Tyler.
You'll learn a lot tonight.
- I'm excited.
- Yeah, it'll be good.
You're gonna meet my dad
and you're gonna meet my mom.
You're gonna meet my crew.
They've always, like,
been there for me
and I'm just, like--
I'm so happy I get to share
these people with you.
- Yeah, that's what I want.
- Yeah.
- So you said you hadn't
seen your dad...
- No, I haven't seen him
since--since I left.
- Yeah.
- I don't know what kind
of shape he's in.
You know,
how he's doing, so--
- How was he when you--
before you left?
- So he's got, like,
a paralyzed vocal cord
from his tube
when he was, like, in a coma
when it came out.
- Okay.
- So, like, he can barely,
like, speak,
very raspy.
He's getting better with that.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then, you know,
he was, like, losing weight
so, like, to leave him and to,
like, not know how he's doing,
you know, I was like,
I'm just hoping, like,
my brother stepped up.
I know my mom's stepped up.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't know how I'm gonna be
when I open that door.
Like, I'm gonna be--It's gonna
be emotional, you know?
Like, family's the most
important thing to me.
- Mm-hmm.
- I want my dad
to be around forever.
I want him to see my wife.
I want him to see my kids.
You know?
- Well, I'm excited
to meet everybody.
I think it's gonna be--
it's gonna be fun.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be good.
- Having you here
is a perfect day.
I couldn't beat it.
[laughs]
I love that smile.
[rock music playing]
Uh-oh.
Wanna go jam?
- Is that for real?
Are we--for real?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
- Come on, girl.
- I'm really excited for Tyler
to see his dad today.
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
- I know that their reunion's
gonna be
something really special.
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
- I'm interested to see
what his family thinks
about if he truly
is at a point in his life
where he can commit to
an engagement and to marriage.
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Everybody now ♪
- Today was awesome.
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
- And hot in all ways.
[cheers and applause]
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, man.
We're here.
This is it.
We're finally here.
Taking you home to meet my mom,
my pops.
- I mean,
Tyler was just amazing today.
But tonight I really just need
to know from Tyler's family
if they really do feel like
Tyler's ready for marriage.
- I'm so excited
for you to meet them.
- But at the same time,
I'm really excited
for Tyler to see his dad today.
I know that their
reunion's gonna be
something really special.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Hey!
- How we doing?
- Hi.
- This is Hannah, everybody.
- Hi!
I'm Hannah.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- This is my mom Andrea.
- Oh, hi!
How are you?
- Hi. I'm his Aunt Bettina.
- What's up, Dad?
- Hi!
- Yeah, man.
It's crazy.
- It's been weeks and weeks
and weeks
since I've seen my dad.
My dad getting sick
and almost dying, you know--
it put a lot of things
in perspective.
It was like, I alway--
I want my dad to see my wife.
If, you know, all goes well,
Hannah could be that.
- Hey!
- This is my dad.
- Hey, Miss Hannah.
- I'm Hannah.
- The real life Hannah.
How you doing?
- It's so nice to meet you.
- My pleasure.
- It was really amazing
to see him tonight.
Yeah, I'm so happy.
I don't know what's going on
with my eye, man.
I don't know, but...yeah.
That's my pops.
- Tyler, you look amazing,
brother.
- Thank you.
- You look good, buddy.
- Yeah, it's been
quite a journey.
Uh--
- What are you guys doing?
- You know, first night,
I come
and I hop out of this limo
and I see her
and I completely, like--
like, freak out.
I'm almost like, "Oh!"
Like, oh, my God.
She was wearing this--
- No, he went like this...
I remember that.
- Yeah.
I was, like,
had this whole, you know,
smooth thing I was gonna say
to her when I saw her.
And it completely
just went out the window.
I had no idea
what I was talking about.
- He was so cute when
I was like, "Oh, he's a stud."
[all laughing]
- You know, Tyler got
selected for the show,
and you know of course,
small town.
Everybody's gonna be watching.
The only thing
that I hope for--
please don't let him get
cut on the first show.
[all laughing]
I think when Tyler
walked in that room
and sat down
with Miss Hannah B,
and the way that they looked
at each other,
I knew right away,
"Oh, my Gosh.
This is real."
Well, I will admit,
you've got--
you've got me worried.
When I look at you with her,
I'm like,
"Oh, my gosh.
He might be in love."
You know?
- Yeah.
- If that's the case,
I'm so happy for you.
- Yeah, no, that means a lot.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
- How's your health?
- My health is good.
I still have a problem
with my vocal cord.
- Yeah.
- But I get up every day
and work hard,
which is hard sometimes.
- Do you feel like you're
getting stronger?
- Yeah, it just takes a lot
of hard work and--
- Yeah.
- Getting there slowly.
You know, like, you know,
you getting sick
and, you know, like,
that was one of the hardest,
you know, things I ever had
to go through in my life.
That was writing--
signing away, like,
your rights to go to surgery,
you know?
Like, killed me, and...
I want you to see my wife.
I want you to see my kids,
you know?
That's why I'm taking
this seriously
'cause this could be it,
you know?
And I want you to be around
for all that.
And--and it's just--
it means the world
to have her here
today with you.
- If you and Miss Hannah are...
It works out,
then we do all we do
to love and support you.
- Yeah.
- I love you.
- And I want the best
for you and Hannah.
- That means the world.
It really does.
- I haven't seen my son
this happy in a long time.
Me and Tyler,
ever since he was just
a small child, have been on
a big journey together.
And it's good to see
him that happy.
- I love you, Pop.
♪ ♪
- I think as a parent,
that's all you can ask for.
Or wish for.
- So how's Tyler?
- Pretty cool dude.
- Yeah?
- Pretty smooth.
He's been great.
- Deep down inside he's one
of the nicest people
you could ever possibly meet.
- Yeah.
You know, knowing your brother
a few months ago to now,
do you feel like you could
see him being engaged?
Like, does that
freak y'all out?
Like, could you see him
really being ready for that?
- Honestly, with my dad
being in the hospital,
Tyler was really able
to run my dad's business.
He was able to help, like,
my mom with all--
everything she was going
through with my dad
being in the hospital.
He really stepped in there
and became, like,
everyone's person to lean on.
He was able to really help us
out when we all needed him.
- Yeah.
- Seeing him now,
seeing him completely changed,
I can legitimately see
my brother getting engaged.
[dramatic music]
- So, of your journey so far,
what have you learned
the most about yourself?
- Um, I was always very closed
off to a lot of, like--
to a lot of people.
I don't really show my emotion,
show my feelings.
I kinda keep those to myself.
- We protect ourselves.
- Yeah.
And, uh, with her,
I was like,
"If I'm gonna make this work,
I gotta open up right away."
It was hard but, like,
to be able to confide in her,
to tell her these things,
like, it was a big step for me
that I can do that
for somebody.
- I wasn't really sure
what to expect today.
But I was excited to see
your chemistry with her.
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you see yourself
proposing?
Can you see yourself--
- This is--so yeah.
It's like, uh--
- I mean, you guys
are getting to the end.
- Yeah.
It's like, uh,
sometimes I think about it
and it's, like, it scares me.
I'm like, "Holy cow,"
you know?
But there's no doubt
I can be that guy
and get down on one knee
at the end of this.
♪ ♪
- Oh, it's so nice here.
- Isn't it nice?
Jupiter's a beautiful place.
- It's beautiful.
I'm excited to be here
with your son.
- Speaking of Tyler,
you got me worried about him.
- Why are you worried?
- Because he had that look
on his face.
You guys seem
so happy together.
Like, "Oh, no.
He might be in love."
- [chuckles]
- You know, didn't expect that.
- Yeah.
- Because Tyler's not one
to let many people
get close to him.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, it's not like
he's had a lot of girlfriends.
It's, uh, been a big journey
for him also, you know?
- Yeah.
Do you feel like he's ready
for what would be at the end,
truly?
- He's 26.
He's at that point
in his life where marriage
is definitely something
he's thinking about.
- Yeah.
- You can't plan
to fall in love.
- Yeah.
- It just hits you right
between the eyes, you know?
But I'm ecstatic for him,
if that's the way it--
it all turns out, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- I think if you have that
opportunity to fall in love,
then there's nothing better
in the world,
if it--that's the way
it all works out.
You would have all
our love and support
that any parent
would surely give, so...
- Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I appreciate that.
- All right, Miss Hannah B.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
- After talking
with Tyler's dad
and him being so reassuring
about Tyler
and his intentions,
it gives me a lot of hope.
- See you, guys.
all: Bye.
- Tyler's family--
- Well, we did it.
- That was so great.
Knowing how he has been
in the past
versus how he is now,
I feel like they know
the difference
and are really excited
for both of us.
- Whoo!
- Oh.
Tell me what you think.
- They're awesome.
- This was, uh, everything I--
you know, I needed and more.
It's gotten me so excited
moving forward and, like,
really put things
in a real perspective
and, like, I wanna be great.
I wanna be, like,
step up for you, you know?
You know, I do feel like
I'm falling in love with you
and I just--
I'm, like, excited
for where our journey can go
and just ready to take off
with you
and make the most of it.
I've just had the most amazing
day and night with Hannah.
[engine turns]
It was everything I needed,
and I'm so excited
to move forward.
[both giggling]
Well, I think I have
to leave you here.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I'm not.
- Okay.
- I'm coming with ya.
I'm coming with ya.
It was so hard
to say good-bye to her.
That fire was roaring.
Like, we had that passion,
and things got hot.
Oh, sorry, Mom.
- [laughs]
- I want to give her
all of me
and I don't wanna
hold anything back.
I feel so confident
about our relationship
and I believe in her,
and I believe in us.
One day I'll be able to say
I love you, you know?
And I do believe that I'd be
able to stand 100% behind it.
I'll miss ya.
- I'll miss you.
- Good night.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Luke is a jigsaw puzzle
for me.
Like, I've got
the corners down
but don't have really
the middle figured out.
- I was chasing sex
and I was entangled in sin.
- Luke is so opposite
of what you've experienced.
- You aren't Luke.
So why--why is he here?
- And later...
- Today is gonna propel
Hannah and I
to a completely new chapter
of our relationship.
You ever just feel
like your heart's
coming out of your chest
'cause you have
to say something
and you can't do it?
- What do you mean?
[upbeat guitar music]
♪ ♪
- We're in
Gainesville, Georgia,
and today is Luke's hometown.
♪ ♪
Luke was the first guy
to tell me
that he was
falling in love with me
and, like, I had an
immediate connection with him.
♪ ♪
Since then, we've had
ups and downs, for sure,
but through all the drama,
I've always, like,
seen the good in Luke.
[squeals]
Luke is definitely complex,
and I wanna understand
why he is the way he is,
and if not, this'll be
the end of the road for us.
- You know, I know that
there's been a lot of bumps
in this process for--
- Hmm.
- A few obstacles.
- Yeah.
- And I want you
to get to know me better.
- Okay.
- So I figured we'd
do something that I do
on a weekly basis,
and maybe you can meet
some of my friends.
- Okay.
- Yeah, every Sunday,
before church,
we have Sunday school.
- [laughs]
- And you're gonna be
a part of it, so here we go!
- Let's do it.
- You ready?
- I'm pumped.
I'm excited.
[mellow music]
- I feel like Luke
is a jigsaw puzzle for me.
Like,
I've got the corners down
but don't have, really,
the middle figured out.
♪ ♪
And I feel like
I can see that
by seeing
where Luke comes from,
the people that made a Luke.
[cheers and applause]
- What's up?
- This is Hannah, everybody.
[overlapping chatter]
- What's your name?
- I'm Hunter.
- Hunter, I'm Hannah.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Hannah.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- You're beautiful.
- Oh, my God, you're so sweet.
Thank y'all so much
for being so welcoming.
- Hey, what we can do is,
if everybody wants
to kind of gather round,
get your seat,
and I think you're gonna
share, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- So, you know, as of recently,
I got to meet
some new people
and just experience a lot,
and I've realized how powerful
it is to share your struggles.
And I want you to know,
you know,
more about what
I've been through.
So high school, I was never--I
was never this, like, punk kid.
I was still me.
I was a respectful guy.
You know, I was starting
to experiment with things
like partying and drinking
and things that I knew that
I shouldn't be involved with.
And college, phew,
it was just crazy.
I was--I was chasing sex,
and I was entangled
and caught up in sin
of all kinds.
And I remember
getting in the shower.
I remember feeling like
I had all this weight on me.
And I remember
just bawling my eyes out
and feeling God talk to me
and hearing Him say,
"Luke, let go.
Let go and follow Me."
And I remember just feeling
like this huge weight
had been lifted off of me,
and I remember seeing,
like, a hole open up,
and I could, like, see
a glimpse and see into Heaven.
And I remember
thinking to myself,
this is where
I need my focus.
This what I need to be
thinking of and nothing else.
The Holy Spirit coming to me
and convicting me,
like, that is why
I'm the man I am today.
So anything that you look at
to be negative in your life,
I want you to know that,
like, God is gonna use
that for a positive.
So that's the perspective
I have for you guys,
and now here I am
with beautiful Hannah.
- Hello.
[applause]
- Just throughout this whole
journey that I've been on,
I thank God
for revealing a lot to me,
but, honestly,
I thank God for you
and for you to open my eyes
to how important it is
to just let go
and be real and be yourself.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
[applause]
- Okay, what we want to do now
is kind of break up
in smaller groups,
kind of casual,
whatever ya wanna do.
- Sweet.
It's cool to see that Luke
really lives his faith,
and you could tell he was
just really happy to be here.
Okay, tell me about Luke.
- Well, I heard stories
about Luke.
- What were the stories?
- There was just...
- Oh, God.
- This giant, bulking man with
a smile always on his face.
- [laughs]
- And so later that day,
Luke walks in.
I said, "All right,
there's him."
- "That's him."
[laughter]
- He's just the nicest dude.
- He's the real deal.
It's just evident
in how he lives, how he talks,
and just--it's just--
he's been a good friend for me.
- You're making me blush.
[laughter]
- It was great to see him,
like, just being affirmed
by other people.
Did y'all sit together
and everything there?
- Mm-hmm.
- Luke's literally made friends
with everybody around here.
Like, it didn't matter
who was sitting by us.
He was gonna go
be friends with them.
- It was nice for me
to also be affirmed
in the good
that I see in Luke.
- Luke loves the underdog,
and he's gonna reach out
to them and just so hospitable.
And we love him
like our kid, so...
- Love you guys.
- It was a nice change to just
see people rally around him
and support him because I have
not heard a lot of that.
- Let's pray for him
real quick.
- Lord, we just lift up Luke,
and we lift up Hannah to you.
Help them to be Your vessels
for Your Gospel.
- Today was a really good day.
I feel like with Luke,
now we have to, like,
continue the momentum.
- Thank you.
- So I'm just ready
to go and see
the rest
of his family tonight,
but I feel like today
was a really good day.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Are you nervous?
I'm not nervous.
I'm excited.
- I'm so excited.
[both giggling]
- I'm really excited
to meet Luke's family.
I feel like surrounding Luke
with people who love him
really brings him back
to, like, who he is
and so this is a great way
to see more of the real Luke.
- Ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- All right, let's do this.
I can hear the voices
in the house--[laughs].
- Hey!
[cheers and laughter]
- Tonight,
Hannah meets my family.
She gets to meet
my dad, Mike...
- I'm Mike.
- Hi.
- And my brother,
who's also named Mike,
and Hannah,
who is my sister-in-law,
which is kinda cool.
My mom, Elizabeth.
- Hi!
- My grandma.
- Oh!
- My great-grandma.
- Hi, I'm Hannah.
- I know you are.
- She's rocking 96.
- Can I sit beside you here?
- Yes.
- Oh, thank you.
[laughs]
- Tonight is huge.
You know, Hannah's
asking to see the real me
and see truly
what I'm made of,
and today I think
was a perfect start,
but there's still more
to show her.
- Tell us everything.
- From the beginning, it was
like, great, great, great.
- Fireworks,
and I actually did drop
a little bit of a bomb
on Hannah onstage.
Um, I told her that,
without a doubt,
I'm starting
to fall in love with her.
- Wow.
- And this is the first week.
[laughter]
There was a lotta downhill
from there.
- Yeah.
- Oh, gosh.
- Like, it was great,
and then it was like
him and another guy
kind of got into it
and then it became, like,
Luke against, basically
I feel like the rest
of the house from then on.
- Oh, that's great.
- Yeah.
- I know.
He had you on his side.
That's good.
That's good odds.
- No, not always,
because there were--
there were times where, like,
Luke asked for it, I feel like.
Um...
- Oh, really?
- She laid down
the law, though.
She set me straight.
- And so...
Truly, for, like, three weeks,
I don't think we really
had a real conversation
other than, like,
me, like, getting on him
- Yes.
- About what all the
other guys said to me and then
being like--he'd be like,
"Everything is fine.
Everything's fine."
I'm like, "No, it's not."
- Yeah.
- And, I mean, it was just,
like, constant me trying to get
him to talk about everything
and trying to break him down
to, like, really talk to me.
- I cared a lot about her,
and I was put in the position
where I felt like I was
walking on eggshells
and I had to be cautious
and I felt like I had
to say and do
all the right things
which is, obviously,
the worst mind-set.
Like, just be
completely yourself, right?
Be real,
and that was something
I really struggled with.
- We told him, "Luke, be Luke."
- Yep.
- And what you just admitted
to is, you weren't Luke.
- Exactly. You're right.
- So why--why is he here?
- I don't know!
[laughter]
- Thank you for putting up
with him.
[laughter]
- To hear the stories
and stuff that happened,
I mean,
that's not like my son.
And I can see Luke
wasn't proud of it,
but I haven't totally worked
it out in my mind to kind of
even visualize how this
dynamic could have occurred.
I hate to think of people
being critical of you,
but there's a lot of things
I just have no idea
what you've gone through,
and I mean this
with all my heart.
If she is worth it to you--
- 100%...worth it.
- Then nothing stops
your relationship with her.
I mean, I don't care
what's going on over here.
- Yeah.
- Is it better, what's left?
Or is it gonna be the same--
- Let me just tell you this:
I truly am so thankful
'cause now, like,
the last week and a half,
my relationship with
Hannah has been on track,
and I'm, like, refusing
to let any of the noise
get into my lane
of me and Hannah.
And I'm telling you,
there's this--
there's something about
the connection that we have.
I can't describe it,
seriously.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And the strength
that I know and I sense
in our relationship right now
is our spiritual connection.
- That's--that's wonderful.
- And because of that, like,
I've gotten to truly see
sides of her that
no one else has,
and she continually proves
to me that she's so worth it.
- If she's worth it to you,
that means she's worth you.
- She is worth it to me,
seriously.
- Wow, Luke.
I would thank the Lord,
number one,
because somehow her heart
is softened to you,
and you know what?
That is a gift like
we could never deserve.
- Yeah, that's how
I feel, 100%.
I love this girl.
I--I--I just, I'm being real.
I can't see this
not working out in the end.
Like, I look her in the eyes,
and I see Miz Parker.
- Luke and I
are very far ahead,
like, as far as emotionally.
Like, we've gone
through things.
But then I also see
a lot of what the guys see,
'cause he could almost be--
I'm just being--
'cause I want to know
more from you.
- We want you to be--we want
you to be fully transparent.
- Sometimes it was like he
thought he had it in the bag,
and it was really frustrating
'cause it came across
a little arrogant,
even with me,
and I was, like,
very frustrated with that.
- Hearing what you say,
it's not who Luke really is.
- The whole thing has been
like, I don't think that's--
- Yeah, yeah, it--
sure, sure, yeah, yeah.
- It's just been hard.
- You know, for him,
it's how quickly can he,
you know, realize it,
and then once he realizes it
and he sees, like,
"Okay, that wasn't cool,"
like, you will see
the most humble guy.
You will see
the guy that's like,
"I can't believe
I was like that.
I wanna make this right."
You know, that will be Luke.
- Mm-hmm.
- I just love him so much,
and Luke is so--
He's one of a kind
in so many ways.
He's so passionate.
His heart is--is huge.
- I've always seen his heart.
Like, I've always seen it,
and so I couldn't
let the relationship go,
even through everything,
'cause there's always just
been something there, like,
when he shows the real Luke.
- Yeah.
- I just hope you know that
what you're looking for,
what you say
you're looking for,
knowing Luke,
I know it's there.
I know strongly
Luke feels for her,
and, you know,
moving forward for them,
it's a matter of,
"Okay, we got here.
"It was bumpy but we're here,
"and now where
do we go forward
and how does that work?"
And that's being open and
being honest and being genuine.
- It's been a ride
with your son, I'll say.
I'm glad I'm here, but, whew.
- I don't understand how it all
got kind of messed up,
but in some ways,
there's a reason.
- Yeah, I've tried to say,
like, I do feel like
our relationship's gotten
strong because of everything.
- It's so funny, like,
when you say those things...
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, if you knew Luke,
Luke's the one that gets in--
like, gets in a fight
to stop these guys
from fighting
and turns 'em.
That's Luke.
I mean, if you want someone
to love you fearlessly,
that's Luke.
What he...thinks of you
is very clear.
He was excited
that you could be the one.
What he's humbled with is,
not only could she be the one;
she wants to be the one.
- Do you think
he would be ready
for the engagement
at the end of this?
- I mean, there's no doubt.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's something, huh?
- So Hannah was talking about
some things at the table.
Um...
- Did you wanna
talk about that?
- Well, and just being able
to open up to her
and, like, why wouldn't you
just be so open
and so willing
to share that with her?
Like, what's holding you back?
- It was just complicated.
It was just hard for me.
You know, I was just trying
to be Mr. Perfect,
and there's a lot of...
reasons why,
but the main reason was because
I was being cautious.
- You've always been like that.
I mean, sometimes,
you're not gonna always
make everybody happy,
and I think you need
to really let Hannah
see your heart
and how beautiful it is
and see you for everything
that you have to offer her.
- Like, I know that she needs
to see genuinely me,
and right now,
I feel like there's nothing
holding me back whatsoever
from being completely myself.
Like, I can look you
in the eyes and tell you
that when I look her
in the eyes, I love her.
[tender music]
Come here, give me a hug.
I see you starting to cry.
- Mm.
♪ ♪
- I love you, Mom.
- I love you too.
- You know,
Hannah's been
completely real with me
this whole time,
and she's shown me
a lot that I haven't shown her,
and there's still a lot
that I have to show Hannah.
It just comes to my emotions
and my feelings.
There's deeper conversations
that we need to have,
and that's just the truth.
- Bye.
- See you guys.
- Bye, y'all.
- Bye-bye.
- They're so sweet.
- But I'm confident that
today went the best
it could have ever gone.
Hey, you.
- Hey.
That was great.
- Was it?
- Yeah.
- That makes me happy.
- How do you feel?
- Um...
You know, I know that we've--
we've struggled.
I have put you
through a struggle,
um, through all of this,
and I have struggled
just completely letting go,
and I just want to tell you
that I am sorry.
You know, we are finally
back on track,
but I know that there still
may be concerns that you have
about us being able to get
where we need to be.
- Mm.
- I'm gonna continue
just to show you who I am.
Without a doubt,
I see a future with you.
Without a doubt, like,
looking in your eyes,
I feel like that I am looking
at my future wife,
and, without a doubt, I can
tell you that I do love you.
[tender piano music]
♪ ♪
- Luke told me he loves me.
It felt really good.
Made my heart
do little flutteries.
Hey, we had a good day
all day.
[laughs]
- We did.
- That's, like, a big deal.
- It is a big deal.
- Like, I feel confident in him
and what he says.
Guess what he said.
- Oh, my goodness.
- "Don't screw up or I'll"--
look at me.
"I'll hurt you."
- 100%.
- You know,
I have the feeling,
that, like, I have
fallen in love with him.
I'm falling in love with him.
[laughs]
- Good night.
- Night.
- Yeah, I'm falling in love
with Luke.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- I'm very protective
over Jed,
and, honestly, like,
him falling in love with you,
I'm not sure
that it's a good thing.
- She asked me upstairs if
you'd be ready to be engaged,
and I said no.
I think this is crazy.
- It feels like
a very impossible situation.
[rooster crows]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, beautiful.
You made it.
- Hey!
- I'm just so happy.
You know, we've been
all over the world,
but today it's just
so awesome to be back.
I get to show Hannah
my hometown,
a place that means
so much to me,
that means so much
to my family.
I missed you so bad.
- It's been a long time.
- I know.
- Last week, she told me
that she was
falling in love with me.
I felt like my heart
just exploded.
It just blew my mind.
I just feel so good
about where we are.
I'll walk you through the town
that kind of made me who I am.
- Yeah.
- This is also
where my parents met.
- [gasps] For real?
- Yeah, not far
from right here, so...
- How cool.
- So there's a lot of love
in the air.
- Okay.
- We have some fun things
we're gonna do today,
but I'm so glad you're here.
- I'm so glad to be here.
- I've missed you.
It's been way too long.
- Missed you.
- Ready to have a day?
- Let's do it.
- This way?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm excited for today.
Our last date
was a really big date.
I told Jed I was falling
in love with him too,
so it was a big deal
for our relationship.
- You look so beautiful.
- Aw.
- I'm serious, you do.
- It's been a hot minute since
Jed and I have had a date,
but he always has something
in his pocket for me.
[laughs]
It's like, "Ooh, what's
Jed got for me today,"
which is, like, so fun
to have a little surprise.
[gentle music]
Oh, this is so cool.
- Yes, did you want
to check out everything?
This is the--
- Amp.
- Well, you plug in, like,
all the mics and stuff.
- That's not what
that's called, a amp?
- Uh-uh.
- Oh, okay. Never mind.
- So this is the booth.
This is where you, you know.
- Lay down the...
- Lay down the heat.
- The vocals.
- The smoke.
We're gonna grab
this bad boy right here.
- That's yours.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
- So, you know, you put me
on the pageant stage
and let me get a feel of that,
so now we're gonna
kind of step into my world
and we're gonna
write a song together.
- Okay, shoot.
- We're just gonna
try to tell our story,
and then we'll make a melody.
- Yeah.
Carrie Underwood, watch out.
- Let's think about
some of our favorite moments
so we have some ideas
to work with.
- What--okay.
So you just write down ideas.
- Right, so just--
- Can I just write down
ideas right now?
- Yeah.
- When you first came out
of the limo,
you said something about me
shining from the outside, but--
- I can't wait to see
if you shine on the inside.
- Yes.
- Write that idea,
like, shining inside.
- Shining, okay.
- Photo booth.
- Of course, photo booth.
And then serenading me
off the balcony.
- That's a good one.
- Oh, I wore these stars,
and then that lady said that
it was written in the stars,
and these are kind of stars.
- They are!
You're written in the stars.
Look at that.
Holding our breath
under the bridges.
That was cool.
- Oh, yeah.
- Cobblestone.
- Cobblestone streets.
Lovin' on cobblestone streets.
- There you go, see?
You're getting there.
Aw.
- You're so sweet.
- She was just a natural
from the beginning,
which I'm not shocked.
She's, like,
really good at everything,
so I love that about her.
♪ You and me ♪
♪ On cobblestone streets ♪
[strumming softly]
♪ Hand in hand ♪
- [laughs]
- Oh, [bleep].
We have to write it.
- Okay.
- This is just making
my day right now, okay?
You're doing great.
- [giggles]
Every girl, like,
in their wildest dreams
wants a guy to write
a song about them.
- ♪ Making wishes
under bridges ♪
♪ We can feel it
in our hearts ♪
♪ In our hearts ♪
- He was just like
playing the guitar.
There'd be moments
when he'd just talk
and I'd be like,
"Thank you, Lord, so much."
It's a great day
here in Tennessee.
[laughs]
[plays guitar chord]
- Whenever you're ready.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Whoo!
- We're just having fun.
We're just jamming.
It's our song.
- This is our song.
- That's what I'm sayin', yeah.
both: ♪ Cobblestone streets ♪
♪ You and me ♪
♪ Hand in hand ♪
♪ Skippin' on our feet ♪
♪ Making wishes
under bridges ♪
♪ We feel it in our hearts ♪
- ♪ In our hearts ♪
both: ♪ We...are...
falling in love ♪
♪ And I...can't...♪
♪ Get enough of your ♪
♪ I don't want to leave ♪
♪ I cannot believe
we've come this far ♪
- Wait, uh--
- ♪ Dun, da, da, da, da, da ♪
both: ♪ It's written
in the stars ♪
♪ ♪
- We wrote a song.
- We did.
Do you ever just feel
like your heart's
coming out of your chest...
- [laughs]
- 'Cause you have to say
something and you can't do it?
- What do you mean?
- [exhales]
I love you.
I can feel it.
- Aw.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- How's your chest now?
- It's beating so fast.
- [laughs]
- How's yours?
- It feels good.
- Good.
Hannah has such
a beautiful heart,
and the way
that she treats me
and the way that I see her
treat other people,
she just shines
inside and out.
♪ ♪
And today, you know,
with my family's blessing,
I feel like it's gonna
propel Hannah and I
to a completely new chapter
of our relationship
and a completely new assurance
that this is right
and that we
are meant for each other.
[gentle country music]
[train horn blowing]
- Are you excited?
- I'm so excited.
Are you?
- Yeah.
I'm really excited
to meet Jed's family.
I feel like my relationship
with Jed is in a good place.
I know I'm falling
in love with him,
and today, Jed told me
that he loved me,
so I'm walking in
really confident.
- Whoo!
[whooping, applause]
- Come on, come on here, y'all.
- Yeah!
[laughter]
Oh, big hug.
- All right.
- Whoa!
So today we're gonna
meet my sister, Lily,
my mom, Gina,
and my dad, Jerry.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
[overlapping chatter]
- My grandparents
are also gonna be there.
- Good to see you, buddy.
- What's going on?
I'm just really excited for
Hannah to get to see, you know,
the people
that made me who I am.
- It's beautiful out here.
- There's Tux.
- Oh, Tux.
- Come here, come here.
- Hi, Tux!
- Come on. Come on. Oh.
- Oh, tricks on tricks.
- He's better than you.
- [laughs]
Hey, now.
Don't say that.
I'll start running.
- Ah, I'm so glad to be home!
- Oh!
- Sheesh.
- Tell us all about it.
Tell us all about it!
- We, uh--we went
to Boston, Massachusetts,
and that was where
we had our first--
- That was
our first one-on-one.
- Our "just us" date.
- We just explored Boston.
- We explored Boston.
- But at the end of the day,
we went and played b-ball
with the Celtics.
- Oh, wow.
- It was so cool.
- We're, like, kissing,
and I have the ball
and I was just like,
"Watch your face,"
and I just, like, launched it
and we're still kissing
and I totally made it,
first try.
- Behind his back.
- That's romantic.
- It was so romantic, yeah.
- Hey, Jed, Hannah,
you guys wanna go over here
and start eating
and keep talking?
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Oh, and sweet tea.
- Okay, now I'm gonna
rip a cheers.
You know, I just want
to make a cheers
to the people that I love
and have missed the most
and a cheers to the person
that I am starting to love.
- Mm.
- Cheers.
- [laughs]
[glasses clinking]
- [giggles]
- Here's to everyone trusting
their intuition
and their gut every day.
When you stick to your truth,
it's beneficial to everybody.
all: Cheers.
- That's good.
- Jed, can I get a minute
with you alone?
You mind?
- Yeah, let's go.
- You don't mind,
do you, Hannah?
- No, no, go ahead.
[giggles]
- Hannah seems to be
a really nice gal,
and you can tell they enjoy
their time together...
What's happening, man?
It's good to see you, buddy.
But it's a little surprising,
you know,
because I still don't have
my head around all of this.
- Isn't this crazy?
- It is.
- Yeah, it's been...wild.
- You guys look like you have
a heck of a time together.
She looks like she's a hoot
and funny and sweet.
- Isn't she pretty?
- Yeah, she's a beautiful girl.
- She's beautiful.
- But I can't get
my head around all of it.
[clears throat]
You know, I guess it's just,
you know, being ready
to be engaged
or get married and stuff...
- [softly] I know.
- You know...
- Like, this is such a, like,
real, serious
commitment, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, huge.
But her and I have seriously
just clicked since day one,
and it's just, like,
continued to grow,
and I started actually
falling in love with her,
which is, like,
wild to say and even think.
- Mm-hmm.
- But, I mean, it's real.
- How do you see your career
and stuff working?
- Um, we kind of talked about,
like, going forward in music
and, like, how there's still
everything that I wanna do
and I was just really now
cracking open the shell
of what I want to do,
and she's, like, all for it,
which was, like,
a huge thing for me
because I've given up,
you know, everything else,
opportunities and stuff,
to go for that.
- Right.
- So she said she is.
And if I'm gonna be
engaged or married,
like, it has to be someone
that's, like, you know,
all right, I'm here for it.
- Right.
- I really am excited about,
especially Jed,
like, meeting y'all and seeing
what makes him him
and where he comes from...
- Yeah.
- He's just been really good
to me and for me...
- Wow. I'm glad to hear that.
- And it's just so good.
- I mean, it is kind of
a dreamy way
to get to date someone.
- Yeah.
- And I know Jed's
just another guy.
- But he's not.
- You are the Bachelorette...
- Yeah.
- And he is one of the guys,
so...
- Mm-hmm. Um...
You know, I know that with us,
it's more than that.
- Oh, yeah?
- I've told your son that
I'm falling in love with him.
- And I'm like, do you say that
to all of them?
- No, I don't.
I haven't said it
to anybody else.
- Really?
- So...
- [laughs]
- Well, that's good.
- Yeah, so, um, and I--
- I'll take that.
- [laughs]
Um...
I know he dated a girl
for a long time.
- He's--I mean,
he lived his life.
Before "The Bachelorette,"
he's had his heart broken.
- Yeah.
- He's been in love.
- He's been--
- Yeah.
- You know, he's human.
He's been through it all,
I think.
- Yeah.
You know, projecting towards
the future and engagement,
do you feel like Jed would be
at a point in his life
where he would be
ready for that?
- I wouldn't have
felt that way before....
- Mm-hmm.
- Just because he's a musician.
- Yeah.
- You don't get a diploma...
- Mm-hmm.
- To be a musician.
- Yeah.
- So, I mean, Jed's had to,
you know, have jobs
and try to create time
and space to do his music.
- Yeah.
- It's his heart,
and it's his soul,
so he couldn't go to work
full-time and do music.
You know, so his path
is different.
- Yeah.
- It's very different.
- When I asked Jed's mom
if she thought that he was
ready for an engagement,
she said that she believed
that Jed had a different path
for his life right now.
It definitely sets off
a few alarms in my head
of, like, is he
or is he not ready?
I know music's
really important to Jed,
and I love that.
Like, I love people who
are passionate about things.
And so, like, I think initially
just seeing that from Jed,
like, really drew me to him.
Does it worry you,
in a way, that, like,
you know, his career, like,
hasn't completely, like
took off yet, but then, like,
you know, maybe being with me
at this point and, like,
does that worry you at all?
Like, he couldn't completely
focus on his music.
- Yeah.
I'm very protective over Jed,
and making music
makes him so happy,
and, honestly, like,
him potentially falling in love
with you, I'm, like, not sure
that it's a good thing.
- I want to know,
like, what you're vibing,
how you're feeling.
- Well, she's super sweet.
- Yeah.
- She is.
- You feel good?
- What I see, I love,
but, you know...
- You're just--
- It doesn't all feel
very realistic to me,
but, you know,
you're the one living it.
- But I'm just saying this is
like real emotions.
I feel like I've fallen
in love with this person.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I'm surprised,
to be honest.
I am.
I mean, I can see.
I think she's beautiful
and I see her personality,
but this is the first
I've seen of her, you know.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think this is crazy.
- I--
- Like, she asked me upstairs
if I thought, prior to this,
would you be ready
to be engaged?
And I said no
just because you're
following your path, you know.
- We've talked about music
and all that other stuff,
and she's along for the ride.
She's completely understanding
of that and supports it.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- And I want you to be happy.
- I know. I am.
- I'm a mom,
a little guarded,
and so, um, to see him...
considering
is a little surprising.
But he seems in a good place.
All the things we do for love.
[laughs]
Everybody just taking chances.
- Thank you all for, honestly,
just showing me
how much you all love Jed,
and I hope that you can see
how much I care for Jed too.
So thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you,
we're glad you came.
- Yeah, we are glad.
- Toodle-oo.
- So nice to meet you.
Tonight did not go like
I expected it would go.
I did not get the validation
that I thought I would get.
- Love you all.
- Love you.
- Bye.
- The fact that they were not
sure that he can focus
on his music
and also focus on me
and our relationship
the way we would need to
was hard to hear because
the concerns are valid.
- Such a beautiful day.
Everything just worked out
so good.
- When I'm out with Jed,
I'm falling in love with him,
but my fear is either
our relationship
or his music will suffer.
I need more time to really
think about this relationship
and where it will go
from here.
- Bye.
I'm just very confused
of my feelings.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- At this moment,
it feels like a very
impossible situation.
I am there with Luke.
I am there with Jed.
I am there with Peter.
I am there with Tyler.
- Are you okay?
- Um, no.
- [whispers] This is crazy.
[whispers]
What the [bleep] is going on?
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Going into
the Rose Ceremony,
it feels like
a very impossible situation
with, like, having feelings
for multiple men
and trying
to figure out, like,
where my feelings are.
♪ ♪
At this moment, like,
I am there with Luke.
I am there with Jed.
I am there with Peter.
I am there with Tyler.
And it's frustrating.
You know, I was hoping
that hometowns
would give me clarity,
but my heart is still open
to each relationship
and doesn't feel confident
in closing the door.
This is going to be
such a hard decision
to send somebody home.
I just don't know
what I'm going to do.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[quiet music]
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
- How're you doing?
- Good.
- Yeah?
- Well, okay.
- How was the week?
How was hometowns?
- They were really good
but all so different.
- Okay.
- It's like, how do you compare
apples to oranges
to kiwi to cantaloupe?
Like, you can't.
There's no clear
frontrunner in my head
or somebody
who's falling behind.
They're all just, like,
doing this with each other.
- Yeah.
- It's truly like,
I don't know.
Where am I right now
in my emotions?
So I'm just hoping maybe when
I walk in there I might just...
know what to do.
- Okay, good luck.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
[overlapping]
- Hello.
- Um, hometowns are...
a big step.
That I was able to meet
the people who made you
and love you
was really special.
It allowed me to see what life
with you would be like,
and I have no doubt
I have four incredible men
in front of me because
I know where you come from.
So thank you so much and know
that it just validates
who I already knew you were...
and are.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Peter.
Peter, will you
accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
Tyler.
Tyler, will you
accept this rose?
- Always, Hannah.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Hannah, gentlemen,
this is the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Um...
I don't--
[sighs]
Can I just--
um...um...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
[all speaking indistinctly]
- I mean, you never know
what can happen.
- Damn.
This is crazy.
It's tough to see her
like that.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
What just happened?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
You okay?
- Um, no.
[sniffles]
[dramatic musical sting]
[crickets chirping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- Um, no.
I can't make a decision.
I don't know what to do.
I don't--
I have four great men,
and I can look at a life
with each of them.
But I don't know if
I've had the time to know
who my person is here
because I need more time.
- You want to dive in.
- I want to dive in,
and I don't feel like I'm...
diving in the way I could
with any of the relationships,
like, the way I know
that I can.
Like, I can't because, like...
[murmurs]
And now it's like I'm gonna
close a door on a relationship
that's not done,
and I don't want to do that.
I don't know what to do.
[tense music]
- You got this, Jed.
It'll be complete baloney
if you don't get a rose.
- I feel good about it,
but, like, also,
you just never know,
you know?
- Well, I just don't think
she sees the other side,
you know?
She gets probably this
fairy tale
Romeo-Juliet [bleep]
from him, you know?
- Yeah, but there's no way
she doesn't see what we see.
- You're afraid you're gonna
regret what you do tonight.
- I just want clarity
every time I make a decision,
and I don't have clarity.
- I get it.
- And so as soon
as I have that,
I can make a decision,
but I don't have it.
Tonight, like, I don't
feel like I'm able to see
if I'd exhausted the
relationship with any of them.
- [exhales]
Oh, man.
- I don't--I don't know
what to do.
[sniffles]
I'm just, like,
really frustrated.
[tense music]
[sniffs]
♪ ♪
- [whispers]
I'm sorry.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm so sorry.
I thought I could just,
like, come in and, like,
look at you all and, like,
know what I was gonna do
and I don't know what to do,
and I'm so confused.
Every decision that I've made
to this point, I've known
that my heart
was completely ready,
and I can't do that.
I can't.
And so...I can't give out
a final rose.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Gentlemen.
Hannah.
The roses you asked for.
[tender piano music]
- I want to continue on
with all of you.
♪ ♪
[romantic music]
Luke.
♪ ♪
Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes.
♪ ♪
- Jed.
[laughs]
Jed, will you accept this rose?
- I will.
- [clears throat]
- [whispers] What the [bleep]
is going on?
I got a rose,
but, to be honest,
it doesn't feel like
I got a rose at all.
It feels like it
was really hard for her
to make a decision
between me and somebody
who's been a complete scumbag
through this whole process.
- Aw.
- Bring it in.
- I don't want to be
in the same category
or even close
to the same category as him.
What is this?
- [laughs]
- He's been a constant toxin
through every bit of this,
and to feel like a toss-up
between him and me now,
like, I just--
I don't know.
I don't know, dude.
- Cheers to love.
- Cheers.
- As of right now, I am
so unsure about all this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Next week on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Whoo!
- We're here in Crete, Greece.
♪ It's Fantasy Suite week ♪
- There is no more secret.
I am in love with Hannah.
- I want you to be the last
person I wake up to forever.
- This is what I want
for the rest of my life.
Next week, I could potentially
be getting down on a knee
asking my future wife
to marry me.
- Really?
- I don't think Luke needs
to be an option any longer.
I need some clarity, not Luke.
- Mm-hmm.
Like, how honest
do you want me to be?
- So let's talk about sex.
Let's say you have had sex
with one or multiple
of these guys.
I'd completely remove myself
from this relationship.
- You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do.
My husband would never say
what you said to me.
I have had sex, and, honestly,
Jesus still loves me.
[dramatic music]
- It's all coming up next week
on "The Bachelorette."
- This is the Pig Apache.
- Okay.
- You always
preflight an airplane
before you fly it, right?
You gotta make sure
that it's safe.
- Pre what?
- Preflight it.
- Pre--preflight.
- Every pilot
has a preflight, so...
you kind of start here
at the wing.
- Sounds good.
- Checking the props here.
So this is
a constant-speed propeller.
- Props which mean propellers.
- Propeller, there you go.
- Mm-hmm.
- I like it.
- Yeah, sounds good.
- We good?
- Kinda like--it's kinda like,
um, testing cheese.
- Kinda like
testing cheese, exactly.
- Yeah, like knowing
if it's a good cheese.
- [laughs]
The gouda, yeah.
You're bringing it back.
- Good...
Yeah.
- I think we're good.
- We're solid, all right.
- Yeah, it's on.
- That sound good?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Oh, there's a little crack
right here.
How's that?
- This is fine.
This is, like, just cosmetics.
- Just--just making sure.
- But I like the eye.
It's attention to detail,
so it's important for a pilot.
- Bird poop.
Is that another one?
- Just cosmetic?
- Calling out
the Pig Apache.
- Yeah, I'm just--
- That's good.
- Look, if it didn't
have anything on it,
then that means
it's just a [bleep].
- So this is definitely not--
- Nobody wants to be
in a [bleep] plane.
- This is not a [bleep] plane
at all.
This is a Pig Apache.